// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the recommended daily water intake for adults engaged in moderate physical activity? ",
    answer: "5 liters ",
    options: [
      "2 liters ",
      "5 liters ",
      "10 liters ",
      "20 liters "
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the ideal time to consume protein after a workout? ",
    answer: "Immediately after a workout ",
    options: [
      "Before a workout ",
      "During a workout ",
      "Immediately after a workout ",
      "ESeveral hours after a workout"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the recommended rest time between sets during weightlifting?",
    answer: "30 seconds ",
    options: [
      "10 seconds ",
      "30 seconds ",
      "60 seconds ",
      "120 seconds "
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the best way to increase flexibility? ",
    answer: "Doing dynamic stretches before a workout ",
    options: [
      "Doing static stretches before a workout",
      "Doing dynamic stretches before a workout ",
      "Doing static stretches after a workout",
      "Doing dynamic stretches after a workout"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is the most effective exercise for building chest muscles? ",
    answer: "Bench press ",
    options: [
      "Bicep curls ",
      "Tricep extensions ",
      "Bench press ",
      "Lunges"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which type of exercise burns more calories in a shorter amount of time? ",
    answer: "High-intensity interval training (HIIT)",
    options: [
      "Pilates",
      "Yoga",
      "Low-intensity steady-state cardio (LISS) ",
      "High-intensity interval training (HIIT)"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "How many times per week should you engage in resistance training to build muscle?",
    answer: "Two or three times per week",
    options: [
      "Once a week ",
      "Twice a month",
      "Two or three times per week",
      "Every day"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the recommended amount of cardio per week for overall health?",
    answer: "150 minutes ",
    options: [
      "10 minutes ",
      "60 minutes ",
      "100 minutes ",
      "150 minutes "
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the most effective exercise for building back muscles?",
    answer: "Deadlifts",
    options: [
      "Sit-ups ",
      "Squats ",
      "Deadlifts",
      "Push-ups"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the best way to improve cardiovascular fitness?",
    answer: "Swimming laps for 30 minutes a day",
    options: [
      "Running on a treadmill for 30 minutes a day",
      "Lifting weights for 30 minutes a day",
      "Taking a leisurely walk for 30 minutes a day",
      "Swimming laps for 30 minutes a day"
    ]
  },

];